1. 
Fxy=w¯
Fx=y⊕w
Fw=xy+x¯z¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯

2.
[xi+F(xi=0)]∙[xi¯+F(xi=1)]

3.
∂f/∂y=0
∂f/∂x=a¯⋅b¯

4.
(∃x,f)[a,b,y]=1
(∀x,f)[a,b,y]=a+b

5. 
There are two feasible repairs: replace “??” with either an OR or an EXOR gate.

6.
Yes, we can compute this as (∃S1S0x,R)[E1,E0] because all we really need to know is that “there exists” some start state (S1S0) and some transition (x) that does lead to this end state (E1E0), and we don’t need to know what those are, just that “they exist”.

7.
F is binate in variables (y,z) and unate in all other variables
F is positive unate in variable (x) and negative unate in variable (w)

8.

9.
Variable z is the most binate variable since it appears in 5 cubes.

10.
The cube list is [11 11 01], [11 11 10], [11 10 11] and it is a tautology